http://www.dainton.com/privacy-policy

Dainton Privacy Policy
Introduction & explanation of privacy and the policy.
Dainton Group Services Limited (Company number 01519778) “(Dainton)” are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets out how Dainton Group Services use and protect any information that you provide when using our web sites.
We may change this policy by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 18th May 2018.
We collect the following kinds of information from people visiting our web sites:
Feedback through visitors emailing Dainton or completing online forms.
Queries and quotation requests through visitors emailing Dainton or completing online forms.
Anonymous site usage information using cookies and analytic techniques.
What we do with the information we gather.
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
To respond to your queries regarding our services.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Controlling your personal information/Opting-out.
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
You may opt out of receiving marketing material at any time by emailing info@dainton.com.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting.
If you do not wish to submit information via our web site, you may contact us by email info@dainton.com or call 01626 835547.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
You have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues (www.ico.org.uk). We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach the ICO so please contact us in the first instance.
Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data.
You have the right to:
Request access to your personal data (commonly known as a “data subject access request”). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.
Request correction of the personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.
Request erasure of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal data where you have successfully exercised your right to object to processing (see below), where we may have processed your information unlawfully or where we are required to erase your personal data to comply with local law. Note, however, that we may not always be able to comply with your request of erasure for specific legal reasons which will be notified to you, if applicable, at the time of your request.
Object to processing of your personal data where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground as you feel it impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes. In some cases, we may demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate grounds to process your information which override your rights and freedoms.
Request restriction of processing of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your personal data in the following scenarios: (a) if you want us to establish the data’s accuracy; (b) where our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it; (c) where you need us to hold the data even if we no longer require it as you need it to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or (d) you have objected to our use of your data but we need to verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it.
Request the transfer of your personal data to you or to a third party. We will provide to you, or a third party you have chosen, your personal data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.
Withdraw consent at any time where we are relying on consent to process your personal data. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you. We will advise you if this is the case at the time you withdraw your consent.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Third-party links
This website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every website you visit.
Cookies
We use cookies to store small amounts of data on your computer, mobile phone or other devices you use to browse our sites. Our Cookie Policy Page explains what cookies are, how and why we use them and how you can control their use.
Accessibility
If you are having any issues accessing or using any part of the site please contact us and we will try our best to accommodate your requirements for information.
Other web sites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over those websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controller
This privacy notice is issued on behalf of the Company Group so when we mention the “Company”, “we”, “us” or “our” in this privacy notice, we are referring to the relevant company in the Company Group responsible for processing your data.
We will let you know which entity will be the controller for your data when you purchase a product or service with us.
Dainton Group Services Limited is the controller and responsible for this website.
We have appointed a Data Protection Manager who is responsible for overseeing questions in relation to this privacy notice. If you have any questions about this privacy notice, including any requests to exercise your legal rights please contact the Data Protection Manager using the details set out below.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any concerns or queries regarding our privacy policy, our use of cookies or any other aspect of our web site:
01626 837014
data.protection@dainton.com
Dainton Group Services, Dainton Business Park, Heathfield, Newton Abbot, TQ12 6RG.
Data Protection Manager: Shaun Duncan
Changes to our privacy policy
Our policy may change from time to time. This site will always contain our current policy.
This Privacy Policy was updated in May 2018.
Home
Head Office
About Us
Jobs at Dainton
Case Studies
Storage Insurance
Storage Advice & FAQs
Packaging Supplies
St Austell
© Dainton Self Storage & Portable Buildings Devon & Cornwall Privacy Policy | Cookie Policy | Terms & Conditions | Promotion T&Cs
Dainton Group Services Ltd Registered in England No. 1519778. Registered Office Dainton Business Park, Heathfield, Newton Abbot, TQ12 6RG.
The Dainton Self Storage price match guarantee applies to equivalent quotes less than 7 days old from other Self Storage companies within a 5 mile radius of the Dainton Self Storage depot. Excludes quotes incorporating price reductions, promotions, discounts or special offers. The Dainton Self Storage price match guarantee cannot be used in conjunction with other Dainton Group Services discounts or offers. Ask in store for full Terms and Conditions.
Thank you for your enquiry!
A member of our team will be in touch shortly to talk about your requirements.
In the meantime, we've sent a summary of your enquiry to your email address.
Use of cookies on this site
Dainton Self Storage uses cookies on this website to help us understand how you and others use our site, so we can tailor your browsing experience.
View our Privacy Policy
Accept
